His actions are
totally unpredictable.
He just lives for fun,
enjoying each day.
ESX-S
HAE JO IS SEEKING FUN
You know what, Jae-mi?
You can never become a mom.
I want to be a mom
who showers
her children with love.
Plants
SUSAN 1982
who showers
her children with love.
That's my dream.
Whenever I'm with my mother,
I feel like a scared little dog.
That's how I came to realize
that I need to be
as strong as a tiger,
to protect
the person I love.
Why are you...
100, .
Is it okay for them to find out
you're not pregnant?
I need to find someone.
It might take me
all over the country.
-You're out of your mind.
-Wanna join me?
I'm never going to give up
on this marriage.
-What are you doing?
-Kidnapping you.
Wait!
You said you'd chase me,
to the ends of the earth
if I ran away.
KINNER S
to the ends of the earth
if I ran away.
Can I hold you to that?
- 9 1018-1580-8975
Jae-mi!
Why are we going to Busan?
We're looking for the sperm
that created this guy!
Sperm donor.
Sorry.
Get him!
If you lose your way
while wandering aimlessly,
it doesn't set you adrift.
It just makes you a drifter-
A DRIFTING SOUL, A STOLEN BRIDE,
AND ONE LAST RIDE
Wanna drift together?
adidas
Do you know what they call
people who talk like you?
A fraud or a freak.
SERIOUSLY,
WHAT COULD GO WRONG?
MR. PLANKTON
K-CONTENT
NEIL